<BooksData><TopExpensiveBooks><Book><_id>666c8f095b1f0e44122b77c6</_id><title>The Perfect Play (Play by Play #1)</title><price>59.99</price><availability>In stock (4 available)</availability><description>Football pro Mick Riley is an all-star, both on the field and in the bedroom. But a sexy, determinedly single mom just might be the one to throw him off his game...For years Mick has been taking full advantage of the life available to a pro athlete: fame, fortune, and a different girl in every city. But when he meets and beds confident, beautiful event planner Tara Lincoln Football pro Mick Riley is an all-star, both on the field and in the bedroom. But a sexy, determinedly single mom just might be the one to throw him off his game...For years Mick has been taking full advantage of the life available to a pro athlete: fame, fortune, and a different girl in every city. But when he meets and beds confident, beautiful event planner Tara Lincoln, he wants much more than the typical one-night stand. Too bad Tara's not interested in getting to know football's most notorious playboy any better.As the single mother of a teenage son, the last thing Tara needs is the jet-set lifestyle of Mick Riley; even though their steamy and passionate one-night stand was unforgettable. Tara's life is complicated enough without being thrust into the spotlight as Mick's latest girl du jour. Tara played the game of love once and lost big, and she doesn't intend to put herself out there again, especially with a heartbreaker like Mick.But when Mick sets his mind to win, nothing will stop him. And he has the perfect play in mind. ...more</description><upc>9cc207168a03470d</upc><product_type>Books</product_type><price_excl_tax>59.99</price_excl_tax><price_incl_tax>59.99</price_incl_tax><tax>0.0</tax><number_of_reviews>0</number_of_reviews><category>Romance</category><star_rating>Three</star_rating></Book><Book><_id>666c8f095b1f0e44122b77a7</_id><title>Last One Home (New Beginnings #1)</title><price>59.98</price><availability>In stock (5 available)</availability><description>Growing up, Cassie Carter and her sisters, Karen and Nichole, were incredibly close -- until one fateful event drove them apart. After high school, Cassie ran away from home to marry the wrong man, throwing away a college scholarship and breaking her parents&#8217; hearts. To make matters worse, Cassie had always been their father&#8217;s favorite -- a sentiment that weighed heavily o Growing up, Cassie Carter and her sisters, Karen and Nichole, were incredibly close -- until one fateful event drove them apart. After high school, Cassie ran away from home to marry the wrong man, throwing away a college scholarship and breaking her parents&#8217; hearts. To make matters worse, Cassie had always been their father&#8217;s favorite -- a sentiment that weighed heavily on her sisters and made Cassie&#8217;s actions even harder to bear.Now thirty-one, Cassie is back in Washington, living in Seattle with her daughter and hoping to leave her past behind. After ending a difficult marriage, Cassie is back on her own two feet, the pieces of her life slowly but surely coming together. Despite the strides Cassie&#8217;s made, she hasn&#8217;t been able to make peace with her sisters. Karen, the oldest, is a busy wife and mother, balancing her career with raising her two children. And Nichole, the youngest, is a stay-at-home mom whose husband indulges her every whim. Then one day, Cassie receives a letter from Karen, offering what Cassie thinks may be a chance to reconcile. And as Cassie opens herself up to new possibilities -- making amends with her sisters, finding love once more -- she realizes the power of compassion, and the promise of a fresh start. ...more</description><upc>07e6810fd3236bda</upc><product_type>Books</product_type><price_excl_tax>59.98</price_excl_tax><price_incl_tax>59.98</price_incl_tax><tax>0.0</tax><number_of_reviews>0</number_of_reviews><category>Fiction</category><star_rating>Three</star_rating></Book><Book><_id>666c8f095b1f0e44122b789a</_id><title>Civilization and Its Discontents</title><price>59.95</price><availability>In stock (3 available)</availability><description>It stands as a brilliant summary of the views on culture from a psychoanalytic perspective that he had been developing since the turn of the century. It is both witness and tribute to the late theory of mind&#8212;the so-called structural theory, with its stress on aggression, indeed the death drive, as the pitiless adversary of eros.Civilization and Its Discontents is one of th It stands as a brilliant summary of the views on culture from a psychoanalytic perspective that he had been developing since the turn of the century. It is both witness and tribute to the late theory of mind&#8212;the so-called structural theory, with its stress on aggression, indeed the death drive, as the pitiless adversary of eros.Civilization and Its Discontents is one of the last of Freud's books, written in the decade before his death and first published in German in 1929. In it he states his views on the broad question of man's place in the world, a place Freud defines in terms of ceaseless conflict between the individual's quest for freedom and society's demand for conformity.Freud's theme is that what works for civilization doesn't necessarily work for man. Man, by nature aggressive and egotistical, seeks self-satisfaction. But culture inhibits his instinctual drives. The result is a pervasive and familiar guilt.Of the various English translations of Freud's major works to appear in his lifetime, only one was authorized by Freud himself: The Standard Edition of the Complete Psychological Works of Sigmund Freud under the general editorship of James Strachey.Freud approved the overall editorial plan, specific renderings of key words and phrases, and the addition of valuable notes, from bibliographical and explanatory. Many of the translations were done by Strachey himself; the rest were prepared under his supervision. The result was to place the Standard Edition in a position of unquestioned supremacy over all other existing versions. ...more</description><upc>396385e3de5d18c3</upc><product_type>Books</product_type><price_excl_tax>59.95</price_excl_tax><price_incl_tax>59.95</price_incl_tax><tax>0.0</tax><number_of_reviews>0</number_of_reviews><category>Psychology</category><star_rating>Two</star_rating></Book><Book><_id>666c8f095b1f0e44122b776e</_id><title>The Barefoot Contessa Cookbook</title><price>59.92</price><availability>In stock (6 available)</availability><description>For more than twenty years, Barefoot Contessa, the acclaimed specialty food store, has been cooking and baking extraordinary dishes for enthusiastic customers in the Hamptons. For many of those years, people have tried to get the exuberant owner, Ina Garten, to share the secrets of her store. Finally, the energy and style that make Barefoot Contessa such a special place ar For more than twenty years, Barefoot Contessa, the acclaimed specialty food store, has been cooking and baking extraordinary dishes for enthusiastic customers in the Hamptons. For many of those years, people have tried to get the exuberant owner, Ina Garten, to share the secrets of her store. Finally, the energy and style that make Barefoot Contessa such a special place are shown here, with dozens of recipes and more than 160 breathtaking photographs, in The Barefoot Contessa Cookbook.Ina's most popular recipes use familiar ingredients, but they taste even better than you would expect. Her Pan-Fried Onion Dip is the real thing, with slowly car-amelized onions and fresh sour cream. Tomato soup is created from oven-roasted tomatoes and fresh basil to intensify the flavors. Meat loaf is as good as your grandmother's, but it's healthier because it's made with ground turkey and fresh herbs. The light and flaky Maple-Oatmeal Scones are baked with rolled oats, whole wheat, and real maple syrup. Now these and other famous Barefoot Contessa recipes can be prepared at home.Ina says that before she owned a specialty food store she often spent a week making dinner for six friends. Her experience at Barefoot Contessa has given her hundreds of ideas for creating wonderful parties in a few hours. And they're all in this book. Crab Cakes with R&#233;moulade Sauce can be stored overnight in the refrigerator and saut&#233;ed just before the guests arrive. Cheddar Corn Chowder can be made days ahead, reheated, and served with a salad and bread for a delicious autumn lunch. The ingredients for Grilled Salmon Salad can all be prepared ahead and tossed together before serving. The batter for the Raspberry Corn Muffins can be mixed a day before and popped into the oven just before breakfast.Ina Garten teaches us how to entertain with style, simplicity, and a relaxed sense of fun. There are notes throughout the book for giving cocktail parties, lunches, and dinner parties where everything is done before the guests arrive. And there are easy instructions for creating gorgeous party platters that don't even require you to cook!With Ina Garten and The Barefoot Contessa Cookbook, you have the perfect recipe for hosting parties that are easy and fun for everyone--including the cook. ...more</description><upc>6478ccb4416e6a5d</upc><product_type>Books</product_type><price_excl_tax>59.92</price_excl_tax><price_incl_tax>59.92</price_incl_tax><tax>0.0</tax><number_of_reviews>0</number_of_reviews><category>Food and Drink</category><star_rating>Five</star_rating></Book><Book><_id>666c8f095b1f0e44122b76ac</_id><title>The Diary of a Young Girl</title><price>59.9</price><availability>In stock (12 available)</availability><description>Discovered in the attic in which she spent the last years of her life, Anne Frank's remarkable diary has since become a world classic&#8212;a powerful reminder of the horrors of war and an eloquent testament to the human spirit.In 1942, with Nazis occupying Holland, a thirteen-year-old Jewish girl and her family fled their home in Amsterdam and went into hiding. For the next two Discovered in the attic in which she spent the last years of her life, Anne Frank's remarkable diary has since become a world classic&#8212;a powerful reminder of the horrors of war and an eloquent testament to the human spirit.In 1942, with Nazis occupying Holland, a thirteen-year-old Jewish girl and her family fled their home in Amsterdam and went into hiding. For the next two years, until their whereabouts were betrayed to the Gestapo, they and another family lived cloistered in the "Secret Annexe" of an old office building. Cut off from the outside world, they faced hunger, boredom, the constant cruelties of living in confined quarters, and the ever-present threat of discovery and death.In her diary Anne Frank recorded vivid impressions of her experiences during this period. By turns thoughtful, moving, and amusing, her account offers a fascinating commentary on human courage and frailty and a compelling self-portrait of a sensitive and spirited young woman whose promise was tragically cut short. ...more</description><upc>54fc03f1e1d355db</upc><product_type>Books</product_type><price_excl_tax>59.9</price_excl_tax><price_incl_tax>59.9</price_incl_tax><tax>0.0</tax><number_of_reviews>0</number_of_reviews><category>Nonfiction</category><star_rating>Three</star_rating></Book></TopExpensiveBooks><CategoryCounts><Category><_id>Default</_id><count>152</count></Category><Category><_id>Nonfiction</_id><count>110</count></Category><Category><_id>Sequential Art</_id><count>75</count></Category><Category><_id>Add a comment</_id><count>67</count></Category><Category><_id>Fiction</_id><count>65</count></Category><Category><_id>Young Adult</_id><count>54</count></Category><Category><_id>Fantasy</_id><count>48</count></Category><Category><_id>Romance</_id><count>35</count></Category><Category><_id>Mystery</_id><count>32</count></Category><Category><_id>Food and Drink</_id><count>30</count></Category><Category><_id>Childrens</_id><count>29</count></Category><Category><_id>Historical Fiction</_id><count>26</count></Category><Category><_id>Poetry</_id><count>19</count></Category><Category><_id>Classics</_id><count>19</count></Category><Category><_id>History</_id><count>18</count></Category><Category><_id>Horror</_id><count>17</count></Category><Category><_id>Womens Fiction</_id><count>17</count></Category><Category><_id>Science Fiction</_id><count>16</count></Category><Category><_id>Science</_id><count>14</count></Category><Category><_id>Music</_id><count>13</count></Category><Category><_id>Business</_id><count>12</count></Category><Category><_id>Travel</_id><count>11</count></Category><Category><_id>Philosophy</_id><count>11</count></Category><Category><_id>Thriller</_id><count>11</count></Category><Category><_id>Humor</_id><count>10</count></Category><Category><_id>Autobiography</_id><count>9</count></Category><Category><_id>Art</_id><count>8</count></Category><Category><_id>Psychology</_id><count>7</count></Category><Category><_id>Religion</_id><count>7</count></Category><Category><_id>Spirituality</_id><count>6</count></Category><Category><_id>New Adult</_id><count>6</count></Category><Category><_id>Christian Fiction</_id><count>6</count></Category><Category><_id>Biography</_id><count>5</count></Category><Category><_id>Sports and Games</_id><count>5</count></Category><Category><_id>Self Help</_id><count>5</count></Category><Category><_id>Health</_id><count>4</count></Category><Category><_id>Contemporary</_id><count>3</count></Category><Category><_id>Politics</_id><count>3</count></Category><Category><_id>Christian</_id><count>3</count></Category><Category><_id>Historical</_id><count>2</count></Category><Category><_id>Adult Fiction</_id><count>1</count></Category><Category><_id>Parenting</_id><count>1</count></Category><Category><_id>Erotica</_id><count>1</count></Category><Category><_id>Crime</_id><count>1</count></Category><Category><_id>Cultural</_id><count>1</count></Category><Category><_id>Novels</_id><count>1</count></Category><Category><_id>Academic</_id><count>1</count></Category><Category><_id>Short Stories</_id><count>1</count></Category><Category><_id>Paranormal</_id><count>1</count></Category><Category><_id>Suspense</_id><count>1</count></Category></CategoryCounts><AveragePriceByStarRating><StarRating><_id>Five</_id><average_price>35.374489795918365</average_price></StarRating><StarRating><_id>Four</_id><average_price>36.093296089385476</average_price></StarRating><StarRating><_id>One</_id><average_price>34.56119469026549</average_price></StarRating><StarRating><_id>Three</_id><average_price>34.6920197044335</average_price></StarRating><StarRating><_id>Two</_id><average_price>34.810918367346936</average_price></StarRating></AveragePriceByStarRating></BooksData>